<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.github.flossbud.ToonTownMultiTool</id>
  <name>ToonTown MultiTool</name>
  <summary>Multitoon controller for Toontown Rewritten and Corporate Clash</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <developer_name>flossbud</developer_name>
  <description>
    <p>
      ToonTown MultiTool lets you launch and control multiple Toontown Rewritten
      and Corporate Clash accounts at the same time. Broadcast input to up to
      four background toons, customize per-slot key sets, manage stored
      accounts via the OS keyring, and track toon stats live.
    </p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.flossbud.ToonTownMultiTool.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/flossbud/ToonTown-MultiTool</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/flossbud/ToonTown-MultiTool/issues</url>
  <categories>
    <category>Game</category>
  </categories>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.6.0-alpha.3" date="2026-05-27">
      <description>
        <p>Project versioning has been restructured to a pre-1.0 alpha line to better reflect maturity. Past releases v1.0 through v2.3.0-a1 have been retagged to v0.1.0-alpha.1 through v0.6.0-alpha.2.</p>
        <p>This release includes the Perform Action logical-action feature for TTR, a unified Held-Key Registry with hold-duration verification, and Python 3.9 CI compatibility fixes inherited from the dev branch since v0.6.0-alpha.2.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.4.0-alpha.2" date="2026-05-04">
      <description>
        <p>New: per-toon Keep-Alive discovery affordance, a help icon now appears next to the chat button on every toon card when Keep-Alive is disabled, with a popover that explains the feature and offers a one-click jump to the Settings group.</p>
        <p>Refreshed Credits tab with new artwork and an updated product description.</p>
        <p>Linux fixes: dark-mode detection on GNOME via the appearance portal with live re-theming, .desktop filename and StartupWMClass aligned with the Wayland app id so pinned launchers group correctly, SecretService keyring probe no longer blocks first launch.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.4.0-alpha.1" date="2026-05-03"/>
    <release version="0.3.0-alpha.3" date="2026-04-26"/>
  </releases>
</component>
